SAMI MDHAFFAR

Full Stack JS Developer



Personal details



SAMI MDHAFFAR



s.mdhaffar@gmail.com



+216 21 000 181



Mahdia Road KM6 Sakiet Eddaier 3011 Sfax



August 6th, 1982



Married



sami-mdhaffar-698427108

github.com/s-mdhaffar

Languages

Arabic

Frensh

English

...

Hobbies

- Football
- Camping
- Traveling

Profile

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or new challenges that I am presented with. As a graduate with more than fifteen years' of experience in management, I am excellent in working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence.

Education

Professorship in Accounting Sciences	Sep 2001 - Jun 2005
--------------------------------------	---------------------

ESC Sfax, Sfax

Photoshop Illustrator Jan 2012 - Mar 2012

ITL, Sfax

30 hours Photoshop and Illustrator training

Full Stack JS Bootcamp Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

Gomycode, Sfax

CorelDraw and ArtCam Training Apr 2012 - Jun 2012

ITLearning, Sfax

Employment

Administrative and Financial director Aug 2005 - Dec 2013

SIB. Sfax

Administratif and Financial director Sep 2013 - May 2014

Med Kotti Group, Tunis

Co-founder Jul 2017 - Present

La Brodeuse, Sfax

Administratif and Financial director Galvo-Laser machine operating

Designing patterns via Photoshop Illustrator CorelDraw and ArtCam

Manager

Rapido Shopping, Sfax

Skills

HTML CSS JavaScript React JS

NODE JS Express Mongoose Mongo D

Certificates

Introduction to project management practices

Mar 2022

Internships

end-of-studies internship

Comptoire Essakia, Sfax

May 2005 - Jun 2005